Here with Broncos' assistant general
manager Reed Burkhalter. Reed, the 2026
NFL Draft just wrapped up and you guys
started it off with a a flurry of moves
at the start of day three. George Payton
said yesterday that those first couple
of day excuse me, round four picks could
set the tone for this draft and it up
drafting Jonah Coleman out of
Washington, Cage Casey out of Boise
State. What do you see with those two
guys and and what do they add to this
roster?
>> interesting he said he was going to set
the tone because those are two tone
setters.
Um Jonah, you know, is a physical
downhill runner, fits our style, fits
what we have in our running back group
right now. And then and then Cage is is
a physical high makeup, high trait
player um that's really going to fit in
our old line room.
And and we talk about setting the tone
for our team in the offensive line room
and and he certainly is going to add to
that.
>> Justin Jolly then you guys trade up to
get him. What was it about him that made
you guys want to move up the board to
add him to this roster? Well, fits the
theme with with the first two. He's a
highly competitive kid. We we really
liked our top 30 visit with him. Just
liked how he carried himself in the
building, around our coaches, around our
staff. Really his infectiousness, his
energy, his competitiveness and he's got
a pass game skill set. And so we're
really excited to get him because of all
those things.
>> Sean then mentioned it was a long wait
until you guys picked again in round
seven, but added three guys in Miles
Scott, Dallen Bentley and then Red
Murdock there with the Mr. Irrelevant
pick. What were those final minutes of
the draft like as you were able to add
three guys who could potentially
contribute to this team?
>> Well, when you get to that point you're
hoping they're there. You know, and at
that point everyone's board looks
different and so they're coming from
from all different angles and and and to
get Miles
and to add to our safety depth. He was a
receiver that converted to to safety and
in his first year at safety he started
three year starter at Illinois and we
got a little inside information from
Palcho and and Pat and um man, they were
bringing him up to us. He was came on a
30 and they were like, man, we got to
get this guy, we got to get this guy.
And so high respect for for those two
players in the program they played in
and and see that extending with with
Miles. And then Dallen, you know, had a
really productive year this year at
Utah.
Um little bit different play style than
Justin, um little bit more of an inline
wide, bigger body, but um like his
upside. And then with Red, you know,
really productive uh year at Buffalo.
Uh he was ball production, forced
fumbles. He's always around the ball,
special teams upside. And so he's going
to fit well in that group as well and
and really plays to the style that that
our defense plays to. Reed, as you look
back on the last three days, I'm not a
pick on round one, but you did add
Jaylen Waddle to this roster last month.
I just how would you evaluate overall uh
this draft class and how it could help
this team moving forward? Well, I I
think the central theme to this draft
class is is the things that we touched
on with the competitiveness. Uh they fit
our culture, all the all these guys.
They're going to raise the level um when
they come in and add to our current
group and and they're going to fit right
in, you know? And so
um when we can add to the collective, um
we feel really good about it. Reed,
appreciate your time and uh
congratulations on another strong draft.
>> thank you.